You. Don't play that out in. The world.
Honey then. You. Put it out
the station and get me
a ticket on the eleven o'clock and cash
the check for me from the front door for
you and I like you Johnny betraying Julie
you better think this over I have been
thinking about their future thinking about
it for days you Roger have been married
. We don't need each other many
Well that happens to two people
nothing that. If.
Whole. Loser worker
for leaving
a old. Daughter won't marry
a whole new look for you
or you knew before you.
Knew for a folder name
a. Dollar woes where
a folder do good for you or you lose four.
Or you lose for ya. Your lark our land.
Lord. Man.
Me. More on.
The angels my land here I am day and man.
Born. And what can I do you.
Reckon department the rack you.
Know about that one of the book Beethoven
yes for this one. Number seven.
Keep it down if. You don't know.
We face the sheet music how do you do
that. Would you mind playing there for.
Me I think black to. Old.
And.
Form. Your Business.
I think. It's
a new job. I've been here
yes it just came it.
Would be nice to dance to. It is.
What's on the other side it's in that
you want. One thing for me.
Or are. On the whole must have fun to.
Watch form.
Of. The night night.
Fire flower mist in.
I'm going this way all
this ice way too honest.
Let's remember that I live here. Oh.
Not tonight. Oh.
Man if I ask you
a personal question. Are. You
going to Victrola inside.
The car. Would you let me have this one
otherwise I'll have to take it home imagine
our child. And have
a machine at home oh. Twenty seven.
Haha.
He. Needs to. Be. New
to. Watch.
Him in.
Her. Her.
Thinking about. An attack on
their. Base that's her to
stand with and. Do you think
in fact. Just wishing.
She could be with you every day like
this. I mean I wish every day could be
a holiday like that. I mean to have to go
back over there I have to go back to work
. Catch
a glimpse. Say
that selling I don't really fill
a. Single A bucket never going
to.
Be there. Can't write can't tame
a state or like the products
of them have to pay.
But they didn't put it on
no nothing found on Fallon.
And romantic. Wrong. As you didn't
really have
a place to ourselves all at just the ocean
the beach I couldn't get. There you know
they all ride to three
more listen to a bit of
a swim be almost load now. In your arms out
in the out. When you're with me or say
.
I don't know when it's safe.
And down the vine do I that.
Is beginning right let's
get to it and down if only
a turn I'm thinking about the
last train. Car left to get to.
The land.
Said Michelle
a very fair bit of it and I don't know
sentiment newspaper you just like any other
night.
Dzhokhar Hey yes yes. Joe.
I know. Just off the
phone. To me. The phone
jack says who follow such is none of your
business so you don't have to bite my
head off my hands. Or you think of
a climax and phone numbers something
he said he might have to go up to you.
To like. He's here he said and
you know what I mean. He said.
No not right I've. Never seen him right
you going to drag it out of. Things and
man I'm going to keep from getting.
The chance. To make
a good thing. But the
Someplace Grammy has been
and will be. On the course you belong here
to non-vital coming from my friend Bill
the way she knows is your drink in the
right off the boat that's what the
bootlegger said to say what oh well what
boat would you like we have all the labels
of an obvious that. You never use it.
You know this part of my turnout
All right I think. Roger.
I thought maybe you know. Pretty
crazy about their quarter.
I'm sort of fond of yeah. It's a great
scene they screw like you get mixed up in
a newspaper man. Gosh you never know what
they're up to they get away with anything
you know but they were due. Course
a lot of fun ducking around interviewing
chorus girls and all that sort of thing.
You're saying here it's fly over here
Miriam Mirja don't worry about me I don't
need any advice I never even thought
about getting. The flu you know.
Let me worried sick about it was I have
been telling him for six months you
couldn't keep away from you would
find yourself married. Oh.
Yeah baby Oh and.
He. Was.
Going to talk you right away I
am but he can't talk to. You.
This is important we're
going to be alone for
a while I know not having fun and
pushing me around all you want to.
Rehabilitate.
I don't be angry Julie
I've been here soon only
a lot happened if i'm gonna come to
a party just before midnight
I'm saying I'm sorry but I had
a million things. And when it does I want
to get this straight I want to tell you
everything. Julie I mean a real break
please quit his job over in Tokyo He's
a Japanese correspondent who got fed up
with the assignment of the weather as I
mean imagine
a spot that left the paper in only one man
the Orient he walked out of the job how
do you know you have this right to
just excited him. You're going to
take. Well that's what they want me to do.
I've got to get here for the train that
leaves at three am gives me the San Francisco
just in time to catch the next boat
for Yokohama. I can't believe you
get Julie Mason the biggie me. Well
you're able Roger you have ability and
I've got I can see that you're going have.
This what I want to talk
to you about I mean it's
a good salary two year contract and I'm
more this moment is kind of opportunity
I've always wanted so like the I was
wondering listening to the reply. Cos I
want you to go that's what's worrying
you. Fee's don't think. I was lying about
that I knew you'd want me to take the
job sure but. Your let's get married.
Let's get married right away tonight. I'll
be the same for you in three months I'll
have the money then. Free money.
While the rest get mad now.
Or Oh but you think I'm going to look funny
the redhead like you out of our lives
here or some other fella came
along. Shooting up the ticket.
Oh oh oh. Oh.
Oh oh. I.
Reach for. It. In Sickness
and In Health sick.
And cherry to tend to yes. You wash
clothes. Do you do.
You are. Maybe. In the Bible jacket or
even on Julie for me they sure
will be. So I've got to get.
My. Dry Dolly. Skim and if.
We want to. Jack can see.
Thank you thank you doctor but I.
Just feel. Like they are going to
pass in the train but
I. Thank you I was and
this is the end of fans
doing not street so great.
Something about me I don't know whether
it's the way it looks the way it smells or
what it. Always makes me feel
I want to be off somewhere.
In some way. I wish this was.
Always me never to think about. I'll never
take it out no matter what happens.
Good job.
Right.
I want to.
Move. On or. Here we are in the.
News on your. Two at an
expected anything might then.
Light something in a theory. Of
the loss of a book saying I have
a saying that you don't. Know. Cannot
read the. Book our.
Servants Dylan they live here. I thought
you didn't lie to me. They're all right
Philip. And you are no place. For
that. But it's only your idea
how do we find it or not be so but I'm
going on be on the romantic nothings to go
to my mind I said I'm different than
you are yet you feel better for.
Your last point. But I've been satisfied
with anything just to be here and know
you're with God but only the best for you
come we have enough this house to let me
have to see into life in pain do you can't
do it again but the believe enough the
trunk you don't think it'll
definitely feel that. It has been.
Simply. I thought you'd like it. Over
the world are we going to cave in I mean
stay right along I still made jaws I
bought at least from an American on my
back I got the least offended Jack two
seventy three games I can never get over
two thousand yeah two thousand yeah. How
much is a oh about
a thousand dollars. Dollar That's
right. How do you do it I mean
you get the money to send to me and buy
a list oh well I got an event. In advance
almost out of it but everybody does out
here on the other day I follow down the
obviously saying he wished April was here
and I did why and he said was that I
got an advance on my December salary.
Oh no. You're not going to be one of those
wise always worried about money oh oh oh
no no no no no wait he said You forget we
still got the inheritance Yes I know but
when I saw it of hate to start off
with a dead fish now you've got
a lot to learn about the audience not to.
Name the place. For sure as well as for
doing things you go to the beach or fancy
you keeping that. They're not always
the burn you say did I say that.
Sometimes I'd wish to Shipley did.
The and.
Why did you tell me one to write me. If
you don't like. I don't like them but of
course I do want to have three and I really
want to have. And this will be our own
. American give. Our
own. She that's great.
To. See the really. Trying to.
Find you love no. You. Must be
a good man. I would return.
Any day when the time of day what makes you
so beautiful how to get out the one and
a mole
a busy year. Well every baby is made to
look like this we've got to keep on I mean
how do you like it. Don't let the wireless
today this is mine the day was filled
with me as
a souvenir of your stay in Japan because
darling we're leaving leaving to pen man
brace yourself the good news Mr Denham is
because good news is when I break we now
belong to that class
a society known as the filthy rich rajah
the Americans yes you got it yes ma'am.
I think one day I do see you didn't
believe me about it did you know I know I
didn't think right. I'm gonna. Saw
that. I'm teaching him to be
a first baseman. Now paragraph to
Mr Mrs Roger Adams socially
prominent young couple plan to take
a trip around the world the paper saying
you know I've quit not by you but we're
going to have
a last week before we settle down to become
good old American parents but Roger you
just didn't give up your job on the paper
for no reason at all this trip and
inspiration to remember the honeymoon
I promised you were going to have
a thing to take for now we've got to think
about the things when I just did this in
the bay because we won't be able to go
anywhere besides I want our baby boy in the
USA where we can get the work started
little paper that a trip like this costs
a fortune. Did you get more than twenty
thousand. You know the benefit we didn't
get the twenty thousand we sold the
property for cash you got thirteen thousand
five hundred how can you
take a trip and buy
a paper now I don't thirteen thousand but
I don't forget this deal lawyers fees
deductions stuff like this just how
much did you get. Trying to tell you
after the deductions we got ten
thousand ten thousand I still got
a couple thousand to build around the end
of it. And you really only got eight
thousand dollars yeah. Well did you
ever have that much money in your life
no matter what your squawking about
at school. You think you are
acting like
a child we should be thinking about the
future. You rush in and pack up your things
and give up a perfectly good job. Will not
mention all. I thought the trip will be
a lot of fun for you I know you're going
to feel like I want to plan on it. And I
don't forget it we won't go. I'm
going to wrench in the pen.
And I'll forget about it.
We're
going
to kill.
Or
guy
. Or gal.
Or guy.
The are
going.
Well that's all
otherwise you'll enjoy perfect
health we are playing tennis in
a couple of months now I've got some good
news for you I'm letting your husband see
you today. That pretty make you
feel better. I've had my hands folk
eating that body out of here
the last couple of days.
But.
We're going.
To have a miserable not
better see you. By for
a chance to do some serious thinking to.
Obvious coming around the nearby towns
town of that little newspaper you know.
No more city ideas like. You
are absolutely right about.
And think of on it and. It's
a little town just north of your place
called Rosalia. If you're here.
It's pretty nearly the kind of place we
wanted. To follow in the new space been
kind of thing
a go to see that we can
make something of it. And
best of all going to have
a home of our own. So I mean I always
call ours. If I make it go to the bank
robbery to get anything you want. To get
to get your friends your car clothes
everything. Can look strange at it. But
I can't get myself to have those things.
But it's even cool and then you're.
The one thing that I. Really
wanted. And had laid.
Back. Atmosphere.
The air.
Well what do you think of this once get
out of prudent Mr had internalized good
joke the good live one outfit like this
your one Oh it's getting your God one in
a permanent job to working.
Families Jack I make sure. As the old
married man like you have the word of your
let me down the list this growing
little paper in the benefit grew
a little on the left there where the
instability for the. What you can eat study of
make up what you think of
it. When you bring it in
cold called no line
a time machine is done when you think it's
time for you apposed to. Miss Julie and
I'm glad to see you. Come on how many it's
about to be deafened wide about seven
Francis first heart I the newspaper
always comes first around here. Come up.
Live in Phoenix. It's with John Yeah.
We're getting it. From our.
Family Well I didn't know you were busy
or not busy. But just been thinking about
fixing up the store I
just want to show you
a new ad we got from the company.
That helps sure to keep all of the
Feel free to pay for really expensive.
Roger back you know you still go
subscriptions so he might not beholden to
late. Oh come on and sit out the gems we
might as well have
a. Stool
and we don't have
a kid around this house. I thought
you knew about that Appleton.
Sure I know about that but I'm
talking about adopting one
sure you can get some pretty good ones that
way you know I was adopted kid much so
. I know that's not much of
a recommendation with internet
survey and so I don't know
a lot of regular kids wound up in
jail. Because Julie I wish you could
have seen some of those little sums
it comes I used to room with it was
a cutest little rascals you'd ever want
to look. I don't think Radzivill want to
tout that I have. One that wasn't
his own I not he's no sucker
he don't want to gamble. On you know what
it's going to be like it's gotta be your
own This way you just walk in and help
yourself to exactly what you want and
there's no guesswork.
You know I've thought
a lot about that I want one
Roger was so disappointed when. I just
hadn't had the courage to Miss Julie you
want to know something he's
all for the idea. Only
a few days ago we were working together
and I was talking with him and you were
talking to him about this sure
he's all for it why didn't he
say something to me but he was afraid to
say anything to you even he is afraid you
might have some fool
notions silly notions.
If he only knew how many there had to YEAH
I AM husband talking about things like
this but the the current air crash manager
please all right the press manager are you
going to be the mother no I just thought
I find the way I get my hands
on that fellow. That I was
going to fight. And. What you want you
looked at knew where would you come down if
they're going to rob you wait
a minute Apple is death. Why didn't you
tell me. What the UN applejack have been
talking about which Julie I told you in
confidence. Well we don't end up with
a sort of you know the you tell me
what you want well you know we were
talking about it what were we talking
about. If you wanted to adopt
a baby you wanted to talk to me yes you
should have told her to write in the first
place Roger Not me I'm not going to
be the mother. Wanted to do due to
a Julie I wanted to adopt
a baby and I hated it I tried to break
it to her gently Oh you're told
that yeah I. Still do I do feel that way
here she wanted even more than you Roger.
That's the way we all feel about it and
I like it too much more than several Oh
Roger I'm so glad if it had been for Happens
act letting it slip out don't want to
know you so better go fix it Prius. You fix
everything else don't you didn't do so
bad
a bad. Julie one thing
about. Not know. When
you get to this place don't get it Susie
arrested right off the bat. You know don't
don't just rush in and grab the first kid
you see you go nuts about it. What makes
you think I'll grab the first when they
show me I've been doing the shopping in
this family to some time now I just don't
bring home anything. You came with this
title you own is not I.
Don't tabs. I have your
letter here. To your own child do eyes
curly head implode chin sweet disposition
we prefer a boy who would like to look
at the girl to. Be you know we agreed on
a boy who want her to look we'll let or
little or. No or now we're going to short
Well this is the administration building
we don't have any children here though.
Everybody wants a blue eyes
curly hair everybody wants
a two year old child will you
tell me why. You see in our case
that would have been the age
of our own child if. I see.
Any way when the two years older they're
more or less housebroken than other one
out of place
at the moment we haven't any
children available adult is
a long waiting list there are three
applications for every child if you get one
within
a year you'll be lucky why you. Didn't
really say we might have to worry the year
after our real parents wait
almost a year. Or certainly
a little bit you see if we we've waited
too long already I know my damage or both
They're young then too we have to
have time to make our investigation.
Investigation Yes You see we're just as
particular about you as prospective parents
as you are about the child who knows him
and. What is your business Mr Adams.
From
a publisher I run the rosie of your
career wish. I beg your pardon
Mrs Green is on the phone we're trying
to tell her. Own. Tell her that we are
sorry but according to our investigators
report we find that Mr Greene doesn't have
a steady income later on perhaps if he
finds himself better situated we'll
reconsider their application. You see
it's not our aim to place our children in
homes of wealth but it's absolutely necessary
for us to have the assurance that the
adoptive parents are financially responsible.
I see in your letter that you live in
the country Good afternoon
that means then that you have
a house and yard. And world No you don't
oh you know we live in an apartment
but there's a nice park nearby Oh here
we go this route to we're putting
a fence around it and our good
to our good bill this large
a sandbox was manna from the roof but I'm
better for it too because if we can get
on the street to say look it doesn't have
to be a yard does it no but you have
a separate room for the child having to
that's very important Oh sure oh yes yes we
have
a lovely room it's practically fixed
up now OA let's fied. Now about
income. Approximately how much do you make
a week well on our good job
offer amazing about one hundred
dollars a week because I have
a look at the books well that's excellent
if you just take that efficacious home
with you get it out and made it into
a so we'll have all the details and then
in due time one of our investigators will
call on you before. You call us
before she comes in to know we
just drop in that's our policy you see we
want to find your house as it really is
every day and nothing is fixed up for
company I see that by the bombs over there.
It doesn't matter if he hasn't got
curly hair doesn't really matter.
He did to her choosing If you're
just me why do you have to be
a big shot when you know we don't
make a hundred dollars a week what
a baby don't you we can't
prove it we don't keep books.
And we're still going to claim that money
left in their claim of your brand of
advice or more.
Than. They.
Usually do you give
a fellow warning. Does Mrs Adams live
here is up stairs or don't bother
I miss all of it from the off and age I
find it when I don't think she's home just
now I think she's in church in church
this time of day Well Lou Good to see you
she Mr Adams go there quite
a lot just go there and see
fine people here. Well
I'm sure that she won't mind if I just
look around to this. New issue and.
If you do how did you
Miss Adams. Subway So if
you want to sit down.
If you know thank you
if. You've come to see
their partner that's
right. This is it is not very
neat at the moment we're
cleaning I see if. That's
our little breakfast
your method if. You
step.
Kitchen.
Think of.
That brings us back to.
The breakfast room.
Kind of picture to cup of tea no
thank you you spoke of a child who
a lovely room yes yes
that's all right here.
This is. Really not any
Chata been lucky to have
a room like this. But I want to
see our yard mixing that up to.
Now. Well I was all over that
expected. This village made here
but I tried out to be strong enough
for the two year old I think I had
a surprise for
a baby came in yesterday down to
hear me because you know thank. You.
So that. That's the reason that we came
to see you sooner than we expected it's
a little girl we don't
want to go five weeks
and three days old Farmer Weeks when
we did speak of an older child
you know you might have to wait
a long time after all
aren't you making too great
a point of the child's age Mr Adams
eventually this child will be two years old.
But we don't know anything about those
little babies. No one does until they have
them and this is such an unusual little
baby actually there's another couple who
has first choice strictly off the record
but somehow I feel she's exactly the child
for you that's why I wanted you to see her
first and I couldn't resist giving you
the chance to bring it with you you know
she's in the nursery you and Mr Adams will
have to come out of the city to
see it. I too like myself. Well.
I can't describe it exactly but she's
well she's like no other child.
Right now with attack. But she isn't
a boy. To Look Roger there's
no harm in looking if
you don't walk around with
a word what are yours
we don't want or. Want
her to them and. The you.
Know All right we'll look.
At that line you call me up and I'll make
an appointment at the nursery I was going
on. With that if you change
your mind you will call me up
Oh. Yes yes. Please
don't short of that other come until
we've seen only I want my dears.
In the in.
The world.
Where. She's like no other
child. That's why I wanted
you to see your face.
Now about him. This is
a day nursery all these youngsters have
parents all except this lovely little girl
. And.
All. Want to grab. For
a girl I mean. Would you like to hold. My.
Hand when you.
Get back.
Or you could. When.
You had to look down but going back home.
On our shores I guess. When we get out now
if your life. Is on the user base
and you know. We can just walk
out of here with it I think it sometimes
happens that way. If we make sure that the
parents and the baby I just
write a check. Well we have
a close one and we don't need to do such
a billion baby don't Miss Morgan will take
care of everything she'll give you the
formula and so forth and then you can go
downtown and buy whatever is necessary.
But. Thank you Ms Allen for being
so kind I don't thank me it
just happens so perhaps before you make
up your minds Holly to take the child you
have to go into history I can assure you
it's an excellent she would take it as on
us we'll take
a chance on her. With the bunnies on. She
.
Wakes up again you know
what that man. Will
leave that baby watcher like
a little dog and I mean are. You
going to shoot.
Him by.
Wow.
That's got
a bit. Out
of the dog that she didn't have
a. Connection say so. I
want to meet up with this thing to thank.
YOU FOR YOU think.
He certainly did
a favor and. We were lucky together. Has
got
a bit. But
do something quick like.
To. Do something good for the baby
suffering. You just didn't want to do it.
All. Over Well I don't just
mean they do something.
You do something you.
Oh no no I'm going to use all of that.
I just want to do daddy.
The only.
Baby that's got. The.
Loans I brought in here with us.
Don't ever do that to me again.
Or
a lawyer. So
what are you trying to do what we're trying
to do trying to get your early favorite
they're going to do it your idea what you
know baby oh well baby my baby. Your big
. Game last night oh well
maybe. They are right.
COMMERCIAL.
And I'll.
Show you don't we go.
Which might. Have been the match.
I can't do anything as long as you're
sitting around here watching me get out and
get out all over you when you think why
do I want you know that they lied about.
Oh I got out of favor All right I'll go
out oh no no no do you see I could drown
the Midwest water oh dear I'm sure.
You know your being. With us
could give you
a nice bed. If it were free and. You
left you keep you just think. Oh right
I'll never be able to do that you have to
get
a bath if you're going to do you
go well you got to do. Both. Oh
what did you ever learn to do that applejack
sisterhood for kids she took to it.
All.
It was
a tell you. I
. Was down
a complete it. If
it could you could go. Could
you go over there is it.
It.
Sure there's
a mighty fine girl. You
know.
I think you can polish man
of the foo foo. You know
we can. Get you we have recovered.
Now watch this closely.
I want to be in Mammoth soon.
You might. Be
down might get
a bit over. Burberry
herds through the only way
you know where. The to
her that you're going to get your horse
your was your good looking I don't. Feel
sorry she wasn't my boy to
me. But yeah you wanted
a boy I did for. Two years daddy's
little girl I dreamed it.
Would. Be Carol now.
Hello. You know
so I get
a second command. Thank you so much for
letting us know you were coming this town.
I was
a little how did you understand. This
your fairy godmother was over. So
you know if. I can plainly see
that she adores her father.
I mean everything to. Do everything
when we going to get one
right you go before the judge the twenty
seven twenty seven you want to see these
charges.
One you can send back to us and the other
you will file with the court at the court
the final case. These are the same questions
at us or last year we just want to
bring them up to date. See religion.
Saying.
Age one year older. I have one
profession still publishing business yes
income income.
Well the same is all over. Not.
All that's the way it is the newspaper
game is all about specially when it's not
one of your own. You have to go to watch
for you really get going. For temporary
I'm having a jam I'm also
a paper mill first thing and I have it
on me by the twenty seventh. I go for
a while. I'm sure you'll find
a way Mr Adams. But you and
I have to prove to the
judge that your income is enough to take
care of Tina and. You know we'd give train
everything she needed most all of and no
matter who else had the stuff around here
. I realize that. Oh.
Yes. And I was going out as
all we can do today. But can I drive
into the train and I think you are
a delight to work with this kind
of air this is so fresh and bad.
And I'm like. She doesn't want to
hear Trina issue to John King.
On Long Island.
In the.
Morning A. Little bit.
More.
You. Know.
The AS.
If you want to pitch in the Tito but Africa
your past option Yeah OK Adam's case
we asked him. To be the one zero zero that
you were going to open come back to us I
was like you'll be doing today I'll
hold you in contempt the both.
Of us of this troubling question.
You know is adoption papers here. It is
you have no incumbent president is that
correct as your. Father says This was all
or you know this case should never come
before me well your honor
I feel that this is
a special case. I kept hoping until the
last minute that Mr Adams might be able to
resume the operation of his paper get
a job but unfortunately he hasn't been
able to do either so I thought I must
conditions ground here doctrine. And this
child will have to vote the often as.
He would drop the chair. Of the
to release papers where it was.
Just
a matter of routine if
you please your honor. You can't just be
a matter of routine for people to have their
baby taken away from this child these
are ours judge those are the
requirements of the law. Yes but you see
we've had this since she was six weeks old
it just doesn't seem reasonable that we
should have to give her back now two to two
strangers Mr I don't. Think it changed
. The regular opportunity to
prove your fitness to put.
You off if you could just look at the record
without any income I have no long time
if. It didn't you make that
clear on the shelf and yes
a lot more idea than I thought
I was however that is the Law
Your Honor she's not
going all the might be
a nice bunch of people probably just
something about on time in there when you
think about the pain as they take
it away from him. I should still be
a good girl and you want to give
up those kind of things but I ask
a judge I'm going to give up your own
child if these are charges much if you've
been born to us. Then I doubt
it's not going to go away do you.
Look Judge we've had over
a year now why we we've walked the floor
over there when she had the colic we've
lost and I just think why
do you every time she got
a tooth we've gone through everything
everything that real parents have with one of
their own that's made all over here about
the inspections we've had to have her way
to charge their bikes nations have difficulty
heard her toys and treasure the brush
they come around regularly and check up
on all those things that they were taking
care of are probably. How many real parents
could keep one of their own I'd gone
through that and you said Danger is
a matter of routine but you were
taken away from us. To our homes
I'm sorry Judge But
when you see we want it's fortunate this
most people would have had one of our own
. But you don't know how bad
people Betty my wife wanted
a child. Wasn't so important to me and I
don't I suppose most men are like this but
children never meant
a great deal to me so I like them all right
this moment but what I'm trying to say
is you're on it the first
time I saw her. She looks
a little and helpless I didn't
know babies were so so little
and then when she took all of my finger
and held on when she she just sort of
walked into my hard judge and she was there
the state I did not go feel like that
I'd always been. Kind of careless
never sponsible I wanted to be
a big shot I couldn't work for anybody I
had to be mown boss that's another thing
now here I am standing in front
of a judge pleading for just
a little longer so that you approve the
young support of little child it doesn't
work quite twenty pounds
is not only for my wife and me I'm asking
you to look at this people judge you for
her sake too she doesn't know any parents
but she won't know what it happened to
see there are so many little things about
her that nobody would have missed the end
of the way Julie and I do love
a judge please don't take her
away from us I've got not
a big shot now or do anything
I work for anybody. Barbara.
Please judge or not said anything I've
got until I get going again. Why did you
never go wrong you should never be without
clothes not as long as I've got to go to
games and help me.
Yeah.
Better than. Yours did. Not last forever
oh oh oh oh oh. Oh oh oh did man.
Know that if you think of fantasy land.
And. The land.
That is part of the man alone Yeah well
look at you go much farther than when she
comes up. To getting him out of jail
she'll be. Well now
let's get
a present. But if you
were given that. What
everybody. Dreamed up
dream now. What about the theory
that the day. After Brian everywhere
day I'm going to die oh oh gosh you know
you're going to prison I don't know what
happened today or more
every day. To be on.
The road to. I always wanted to have life.
I'm going to like
a dog. And this is the magical
Apple. I have to have.
I guess what this say yes. If. It's
beautiful Last time I always figured
the Persian cat had duty to thank you.
This is for me from you. That's what his
penis. Right back you reckon
a place you love grandkids OK You
and Dad baby daddy to learn.
To read is good so we really thank you
come on that's for that what if the I go.
Into granny come and get it girl through
the group. You know if you pull it out of
my own home and I didn't
have to cook at home.
But
a. Room. There
we shortchange the complexity lab bird would
serve and then. What you do in school
today. Wow most for God hours I'm
going to be in the Christmas clearly.
Christmas play what are you going to do
and what they may tell them what to do
that's one of the long he'll be fun but
you know OK I was costume I don't need
a costume nobody sees me nobody
see shoe I have to wear is
a cream distance from sneakers I'm you
go I'm away off behind the scenes
you know me you're my vice he's
happy came seen as he gives
a sound hiking. Why do you have to
wear the sneakers the sneakers you
saw me crying doc up in the sky. And take
a big damn for me then when I get over the
manger I'm Staff. Just seeing the one my
two incomes I sing lack of when I
speak after quietly next to when. I
get to be
a main job in the Larry
manger suit that same name of
course sure I'm good see in the head and
how they. Time and turn it to you Oh
Oh no darling be here no drama at all.
Oh my God Oh brother what
happened was. You see that what.
You think that they can do you. Have. A.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY do the very
birthday you too little you.
Ah.
Ah. Ah.
Ah ah.
Man.
The.
World the good.
The old. The Nann.
I think now.
If I was talking to her she said she did
fine while you were better than all the
rest of them put together. On it.
I don't know if. This maybe. I
don't know what it is that you.
The.
What.
Do play stuff that door one day.
I wish you would. Get out
of to get some fresh air.
And that someone downstairs and.
Someone of Iran tell.
Me Are you sure that does
not all right here on the.
Right by name and fasten it.
Have there always been be
a night like this. I do hope we just
want to tell me the Christmas Friday.
I already don't get it round three. Our
cars are about trucks I'll drive you over
tonight oh very kind of you wouldn't be
too much trouble to.
Get stuff out of bed there to crank it.
Down.
I can't thank you enough if you only
knew what do you think if you do it.
Let's get out of.
What's the matter.
If you're on hold. Roger
I'm not coming home.
I don't ever want to see anything
or anyone that reminds me. Of.
The for.
Their. Marriage Love Her
parents. Her.
Her. Room for me
to. Warm my
order to me.
Who was. Taking us.
All in those homes bad
take you back. Yes they do
take event. Which when you
which ones you believe
preempt. I can't seem to divide
them. They belong to both of us.
Guess I'll just leave them. Well I
was less than downstairs there.
I can remember just as clear the first
time I ever saw you. Roger brought you for
me if. I was cast in pound no
machine. Judy didn't know it all to
get to know each other so well and. To get
the rest of the things out the better.
I know but to me. I'm very
bad or you should leave me.
Well I just say it I mean it's all true I
haven't done any one of the big things
are playing to do for you right
where we started still struggling
to let you down all
around. Well I needed to
make it one hundred percent was for
you to leave me and I can't think of
a reason and I will feel
not to. Look surely.
Not looked at it is just us where lect as
far as our being together is concerned
when something really came along that
hit us hard enough we couldn't face it
together.
I needed you an awful lot these last
few days but you've been miles away
I've been entirely alone. Right here
in this room with you on the road.
I wish I could do something real
Putu it just hasn't worked out.
I did We're going to tell me. Things are
wonderful until this happened to us.
I don't know I. Just have to just have
been able to think straight the last few
days. She was never sick
before then boom all of
a sudden it was all over. And there was
only some way that people could know
a few days ahead what was going to happen.
When the day before she was take the six
you asked me for
a quarter but we're going to have it.
She has been taken to the movies and I
thought no one was going to be busy.
It was the same with me. I was
trying to enjoy
a costume and. She was so excited you
couldn't stand still. I scolded that.
I said. The test on you again. I never
did.
Into their the springs thing
Mrs Adams said we have
a little boy who is just two years old.
But it's the oddest thing he's the exact
image of the youngster you asked for when
you first wrote to me here
demanding. That you know.
OK. It's. Just.
Another couple has the right
to see him he's. Such
a baby that I thought perhaps you. Might.
I'm done with this. Please don't let that
other couple Steven to we do what. I
want my D.H.
. Came
. Over to his or better look
up the kid again and he
took one of the little fellow falling down
the stairs and breaking news up. Just to
get
a good laugh and credit. To me two years
on him sleeping that he can assure. You
we would have to pick the
teams are. Going to over
a necklace. For the good luck to freak.